HARSHITA NADKAR

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a Graduate and with hands of experience on Cisco Routers, Cisco Switches, Real Network, Microsoft Servers as well as freelance teaching experience has help me learn a lot a networking field. I am looking forward to work with companies where I can learn, work and grow professionally and personally.

EXPERIENCE

Network Support Engineer, 12/2021 - Current Movate Technologies - Hyderabad, India

 Presently working as L1 engineer with Zsclaer process handling and resolving tickets with Zscaler process.

Sr. Associate Ops, 05/2019 - 03/2021 Wns Global Services - Pune, India

• I was a Senior Associate OPs handling the verification background process as HireRight.

CCE, 08/2018 - 02/2019 Credence Resource Management - Pune, India

• I was handling US customers with their Medical Insurance.

CCE, 03/2017 - 03/2018 Concentrix - Kolkata, India

• I was handling the domestic process with Maruti Insurance dealing with car insurance.

Head Sales Co-ordinator, 03/2014 - 12/2017 Syska Company - Pune

• In this domain, I was handling all products of Samsung Mobile Accessories. It was a B2B process.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Computer Science, Computer Science, 2012 AISECT COLLEGE Dr. C.V. Raman University - Indore, MP

• [Degree] Graduate

Certificate of Higher Education, Biology, 2008 St.Theresa H.S.School - Indore, MP

Certificate of Higher Education, 10th, 2006 Shishu Vikas High School - Kolkata, WB



CONTACT

Address: Hyderabad, India, 500032

Phone: 8017511801

Email: hnadkar26@gmail.com

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- RIPV2
- Routing
- RIPV1
- OSPF, EIGRP, Static routing
- Routing Trunking Access List, NAT, PAT, ACL, Frame-Relay
- Spanning-Tree, VLAN, Switching, RSTP, PVST
- Inter-VLAN routing
- Subnetting and IP Addressing
- OSI Model, VTP,
- Pruning, HSRP and VRRP
- TECHNICAL SKILLS
- LAN/WAN Routing, Multi-Layer switching, WAN Equipment, TCP/IP
- Switching:-VLAN, STP, VTP
- Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Marathi and Bengali

INTERESTS

Hobbies: , Playing badminton, Listening and singing song, Dance

CERTIFICATIONS

- Completed CCNA, CCNP R &S Training on real time Cisco router and Switches from I-MEDIATA-Pune
- Zscaler Certified Cloud Administrator Internet Access ZCCA-IA
- Zscaler Certified Cloud Professional Internet Access ZCCP-IA

English: First Language Hindi: C2 Bengali: C2 Proficient Proficient Marathi: C2 Proficient

STRENGTHS

- Hard-working
- Open Minded
- Responsible
- Creative
- Punctuality
- Strong-Communication Skill